( NARRATOR SPEAKING )
( WHOOPING )
( LAUGHING )
- Oh , yeah ! - Hook them horns , baby !
We are on our way to the biggest party of the world .
Yeah !
( ROCKMUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO )
( PHONE RINGING )
Red River Rock ' n ' Roll Request Line . This is Stretch .
WOMAN : That 's for Glen .
And could you tell the girls at Mesquite High just to leave him alone ?
STRETCH : Got it , and I believe it . Glen is off-limits now .
This is Stretch on an open request line on K-OKLA in Burkburnett , Texas ,
Red River Rock ' n ' Roll , from the tip-top of the Dallas Fort Worth Metroplex .
( ROCKMUSIC PLAYING )
Heck , let 's give Stretch a call and see what she says .
( LAUGHING ) What kind of name is Stretch ?
No idea .
( PHONE RINGING )
Red River Rock ' n ' Roll Request Line . This is Stretch .
BUZZ : Yo , Stretch ! It 's the one and only Buzz .
And Rick the Prick !
( LAUGHING )
And from all the senior boys at Wheeler High to all the senior girls ,
who are so stuck-up , play You 're on the road to nowhere .
No , you mean , We 're on the road to nowhere .
No , baby .
We 're on the road to Texas-OU Weekend in Dallas !
You 're on the road to nowhere !
Hook them horns , baby !
( WHOOPING )
Real funny , guys .
Okay , you wanna hang up now ?
Tying up the line . Hey , come on .
- No way , baby ! - We got a lot more requests !
Hey , check it out , dude .
BUZZ : Let 's play a little chicken with the farmer here .
( BOTH WHOOPING )
- Come on , baby ! Come on ! - Come on !
( LAUGHING )
Come on , man .
( HORN HONKING )
( BOTH LAUGHING )
Come on !
( BOTH WHOOPING )
( HORN HONKING )
( WHOOPING )
- Hot damn ! - Hook them horns !
That was great ! That was great !
You got that , babe ? Hot line ?
Buzz : You better stick with us , baby !
( BOTH LAUGHING )
Yeah . Later , sports . Just hang up , okay ?
BUZZ : No way !
( LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY )
Hook them horns !
( WHOOPING )
- L.G. ! - Damn it , I 'm trying , darling .
Don 't call me darling , damn it .
( LAUGHING )
( ROCKMUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO )
( EXCLAIMS )
It 's 8 : 11 , Texas-time , on a Friday night .
I know nobody 's listening because y 'all are all zooming ,
but I got a shot of hot rock ' n ' roll for you anyway .
( PHONE RINGING )
( ROCKMUSIC PLAYING )
K-OKLA , Red River Rock ' n ' Roll Request .
What it is , Stretch ? This is the Buzz again .
Not again . Hang it up , lame-o . Go call your mother .
Yeah , yeah , talk dirty . But this is for Rick the Prick .
He wants to hear " Bright Lights , Big Titties . "
Wrong . I don 't want to hear it . I want to see it !
Bright lights , big titties !
( EXCLAIMS )
L.G. ? L.G. , get in here , please .
( RICK CHEERING )
( HORN HONKING )
What the fuck ?
Are you crazy ?
Back up , pig fucker !
Come on . Hurry up . Get out of here !
- RICK : Oh , my God ! - They gotta hang up .
RICK : Step on it !
- Shit ! What the fuck ? - Come on , hurry up !
STRETCH . : Hang up !
( LEATHERFACE YELLING )
- What the hell is that ? - Look , it 's some kind of geek .
- BUZZ : The geek 's got a ... - Come on . What is that ?
- BUZZ : Shit ! - Come on . Get out of here .
- Where 'd he come from ? - I don 't believe this shit !
RICK : Just keep driving . Come on .
- Hey , let 's go . Come on . - BUZZ : What the hell is that ?
- Go on ! What 's he doing ? - BUZZ : God damn it !
What 's he got there ?
BUZZ : Jesus Christ !
- What ? - Come on . What is that ?
- I don 't believe this shit ! - Come on !
RICK : You can do it ! Come on !
Oh , God . Oh , God . Oh , God !
( RICK SCREAMING )
- Holy shit ! - RICK : Come on , get out of here !
RICK : He 's got a fucking chainsaw !
( RICK YELLING )
( RICK SCREAMING )
( HOOTING )
( BOTH SCREAMING )
- Sounds like a buzz saw . - Buzz saw ?
Hey , hang up , man .
Hang up . Hang up , hang up , hang up , hang up , hang up , hang up , hang up !
Get him . Shoot the bastard . Get him . Shit !
( HOOTING )
Fuck ! Shoot that motherfucker , yeah !
( LAUGHING )
( GRUNTING )
Shit ! Keep back ! God !
Son of a bitch ! Shit !
( BOTH SHOUTING )
( GUN FIRING )
Missed us , assholes .
( SCREAMING )
( CAR CRASHING )
What ? It just cut off .
Did you do that ? What happened ?
It 's like super feedback .
Just put the underwoofer across the overflapper .
I don 't know .
Just went dead air .
MAN 1 : I want the license plate . MAN 2 : No problem .
All right , now , ease up here .
MAN 2 : You go get your pictures .
Watch out , Bob .
MAN 2 : All right , keep the tension on that line .
MAN 3 : Hey , loosen that chain . We need some slack .
MAN 2 : Easy . Easy .
( SIREN BLARING )
You , get out of there !
WOMAN ON RADIO : Three-zero .
Cowboy , get away from there . This is an accident scene .
The area is restricted .
- Not gonna tell you ... - It 's all right . It 's all right , Wendell .
Lieutenant Enright , sir .
We heard you might be headed this way . Did you come over for the big game ?
You know why I 'm here .
Yes , sir , something about the chainsaw killers ,
your brother 's kids killed .
But that was 14 years ago , sir , way down in South Texas .
Now , these are other kids .
This is just an accident .
Just a couple of wild punks out raising hell .
Yep .
One of those boys is so wild sawed his own head off
going 90 mile per hour .
( CHUCKLES )
Hell .
Hell 's exactly what they raised .
No , sir , that information 's off the record .
You know , sir , this is always a pretty hairy weekend for Dallas .
Whole lot of folks come to town and don 't give a damn about football .
You know , they just wanna go blood crazy for a few and riot .
You know what " riot " means . You were a Ranger .
I can 't hardly keep them down by law , and if ...
If you go around promoting this chainsaw ...
Try to speak plain .
Saves time .
( GRUNTS )
I have authority
from the DA 's office to put you right back on the next plane to Amarillo .
Well , you just do that , son . I 'd like to see that authority .
All right , Lieutenant Enright , what 's your deal ?
All right .
I 'm gonna ask some questions .
Put it in the press . Get it in the news .
Any information about this accident
and maybe some witnesses .
Yes , sir , I know some old boys at the paper .
We 'll get your story out for you .
Brazos .
Brazos !
Remember the Alamo , cowboy .
( ALL LAUGHING )
( ROCKMUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO )
MAN 1 : I won !
( MAN WHISTLING )
MAN 2 : Come on !
Asshole .
( WHOOPS )
You need a witness ? I 'm a witness .
This Mercedes ? I think I was talking to those kids when it happened .
No way was that an accident .
- You saw it . - No , but I heard it .
You can listen . It 's here on tape .
( LAUGHING )
Regulations . We gotta record all the call-ins .
End of the night , we wipe the tapes ,
but I kept this one just ' cause ... It just got to me .
We got professionals working on this ...
I didn 't know what I 'd heard , but I read your story .
- What you 're looking for is on this tape . - ... so don 't fool with it .
You can slow it down now .
STRETCH : Um ...
You 're just a joke in this morning 's paper .
" Cowboy chases Chainsaws 14 years . "
" Dallas police refuse comment . "
Like you 're , you know , hung up on something crazy .
But I believe you . I might be the only believer you got .
- Cause it 's right here . - What is ?
Right on here , those kids getting killed .
Now , this is evidence , sort of , right ?
Yeah , it 's time for you to go home .
- No , wait a minute , wait a minute . - Come on .
Look , I came here because I thought I could help you .
I deejay this dumb show on K-OKLA up in Burkburnett ,
but people listen to me all across North Texas .
Now , I could put you on the radio ,
get people to believe you , get you some help .
You 're gonna get in my way .
- Don 't you get in my way . - No , I 'm already right in the middle of this .
This is my chance to stop playing head-banging music
and do something real .
Well , I don 't need anybody to stand with me ,
all right ?
You can 't do it alone .
( ENRIGHT CHUCKLES )
I got a perfect willingness to die .
That gives me a moral on this bunch of mad dogs .
They live on fear . They thrive on it .
I ain 't got no fear left .
( SPEAKS SPANISH )
I ain 't got no fear , Lord .
( COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO )
( PEOPLE CHATTERING )
( MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY )
- Hardass . - Hardass ? Me ?
Well , maybe a semi-hardass , but I got a soft heart .
Looky .
- Built you a little fry house . - L.G. !
What , darling ?
Oh , L.G.
( TRIANGLE RINGING )
Okay , everybody , hush up . Listen up , y 'all .
The Texas-OU Chili Cook-off champion is
from Norman , Oklahoma ? No .
( PEOPLE CHEERING )
Waco , Texas ? Mmm-mmm .
Tulsa ? Nope .
- Pardon me . - Austin ? Uh-uh .
He 's Dallas ' favorite caterer . I think he 's kind of cute .
The Last Round-up Rolling Grill Chef ,
Drayton Sawyer !
( ALL CHEERING )
( PEOPLE WHISTLING )
Drayton !
ALL : Drayton ! Drayton ! Drayton ! Drayton !
WOMAN : Way to go , Drayton !
It 's the second year in a row . This year , Drayton ,
you 've got to tell the secret of that fabulously tasty chili !
No secret . It 's the meat .
Don 't skimp on the meat .
I got a real good eye for prime meat .
Runs in the family .
( CHUCKLING )
( EXCLAIMS )
It 's one of those hard-shell peppercorns .
( PEOPLE LAUGHING )
I gotta say , I love this town .
This town loves prime meat !
( PEOPLE CHEERING )
( ALL APPLAUDING )
So there 's the big story . Texas clobbers Oklahoma in chili .
This is Stretch , your fearless reporter , live from Dallas .
( MARCHING BAND PLAYING )
( MAN SPEAKING ON RADIO )
STRETCH : Now , be sure to watch your drinking and driving
on this wild and woolly Texas-OU Weekend .
This is Stretch , on K-OKLA ...
( PHONE RINGING )
Cut-Rite .
No , C.L. , I ain 't seen Fletcher .
Well , last Friday .
Well , hell , he 's on the road , then .
Well , don 't believe me , then . Fine .
C.L.
No .
I 'll be with you in just a minute , sir .
Now , you 're getting as mean as a sting bat , C.L.
CLERK : No , hell , don 't call back .
No , don 't you call back . I got a business here ,
and Fletcher ain 't none of my business .
Damn !
( MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO )
What can I do you for ?
Well , don 't you wanna test them ? There 's gas in them .
Get them suckers a time or two .
( MOTOR WHIRRING )
Oh , my kid banana .
Damn , what is he doing ?
( CLERK LAUGHING )
Now , this is very hard to believe .
I 'd like you to play that tape , missy .
Come all the way up here to Burkburnett . No shit !
Yeah .
Oh , you wanna hear it now .
I wanna hear it on the radio .
On your show .
Uh-uh .
I don 't think it 'd be legal to do that .
FCC regulations , those things .
Well , you just figure out how to do it and do it .
You bend the rules . I don 't know .
( CHUCKLES )
- Why ? - Because the killers are here .
Kill sites have been clustered all over Northeast Texas the last two years .
The laws , they shy away from piecing it together as murder .
They call it accidents , disappearances .
You got that last slaughter on tape . You play it on the radio .
Maybe then , the laws will stop trying to shut me up and start helping me .
Besides , it 'll give you something real to do .
You said you were gonna do this alone .
( SIGHS )
I need your help , missy .
Well ,
you can call me Stretch , Mr. Enright .
Well , now , you can call me Lefty .
It 's mighty nice doing business with you .
- Thanks . - All right .
You have a nice day , now .
You , too .
( COOK LAUGHING )
Number one again !
Drayton did it again . Number one .
Number one ! The Sawyers are number one !
( LAUGHING )
Number one .
( RADIO SHOW THEME PLAYING )
So here 's a special request we 're doing this afternoon and tonight .
You steady listeners know we 're playing this every hour .
This is for Lefty .
BUZZ . : Hog fucker ! Son of a bitch !
( CHAINSAWBUZZING )
( PHONE RINGING )
( LAUGHING )
Last Round-up Rolling Grill . We 're still number one .
I told you , boys , and Hold you .
Don 't call on this phone . Now , damn it , get off .
What ? What 's on the radio ?
Now , don 't bullshit me . I can 't ...
I won 't ... All right , what station ?
This ain 't no joke , boy ?
Then I 'm tuning it in .
BUZZ : Hog fucker ! Son of a bitch !
( CHAINSAWBUZING )
You two nap-haired idiots .
You 've done it again !
You coon shits ! You fudge-packers !
You 'll be the death of me yet !
( LAUGHING )
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
RICK : Missed us , assholes .
( PHONE RINGING )
( RICK SCREAMING )
K-OKLA .
Come on , Lefty . Where are you ?
( CAR CRASHING )
This concludes the broadcast day for K-OKLA in Burkburnett , Texas ,
Red River Rock ' n ' Roll .
In New York , it 's 1 : 00 a.m. , still fun city .
In LA , 10 : 00 at night , party time .
But deep in the heart of Texas , it 's 12 : 00 midnight .
Ain 't nothing going on .
( STAR-SPANGLED BANNER PLAYING )
It 's another cussing caller .
Your little ass is gonna be in big trouble over that tape , girl .
Nope .
( SIGHS )
Sure got a lot of complaints , darling .
L.G. , it was a request , right ? It 's listed in the logs as a request .
People complain about the request every night , right ?
Uh-huh .
Wanna go for coffee at Big State ?
Nope .
Huh , I guess you 're waiting on this guy , Lefty ?
L.G.
( SIGHS )
Night , L.G.
Good night .
God damn it !
( HAWKS )
( ROCKMUSIC PLAYING )
Shit !
( PHONE RINGING )
K-OKLA , this is Stretch .
Hello ?
Hello , Lefty ?
( PHONE CLICKS )
( DIAL TONE DRONING )
( METAL CLANGING )
( DOOR OPENS )
L.G. ?
( CLATTERING )
Lefty ?
( CHOP-TOP GROANING )
I wanna ...
I wanna buy some radio-ad time .
Are you fucking crazy ? We are closed !
Off the air till tomorrow . You 'll have to just come back .
No , but ... But , yeah , but ...
( EXCLAIMS )
So this is radio land , huh ? The infinite turnover ?
The waves through the ether fuzz roll on forever .
( MIMICKING ROAR )
Can 't close that . Hi , I know what you 're thinking .
" This is weird . Hope I can handle it . "
( LAUGHS )
You know ,
you 're my fave .
Me and Bubba , my little brother , we listen to you every night .
Music is my life .
You know , you 're my fave ,
but I get too embarrassed to phone in my request .
It 's too disembodied , you know ?
But
( FLESH SIZZLING )
... now that we 're here in flesh and blood ,
I could maybe make a request , and it 'd still count , huh ?
Uh-huh . Sure . Mmm-hmm .
Well , what about
Iron Butterfly ?
( LAUGHING )
You know , like " In-A-Vida-Da-Gadda , Baby ? "
Oh , it 's heavy ! You know ,
I 've never been to a radio station before .
Do you think you could do me a tour , huh ?
Tour ?
Tour . Sure . Mmm-hmm , sure .
But seriously quick , and it ends at the exit sign .
Oh , boy ! Okay , yeah , sure !
Okay , your tour . Here 's your tour . Here 's your tour . Here 's a lamp .
Yeah , lamp .
Here 's a typewriter .
( EXCLAIMS )
- Rubber man . - Uh-huh . Rubber man . I like him .
Armadillo . Here 's Mr. Shark .
Oh , Mr. Shark !
( LAUGHING )
- Here 's some flowers . - Flowers .
- Rolodex . - Rolodex .
Here 's a lamp .
( GRUNTS )
And there 's the exit sign . Tour 's over .
( CHUCKLING )
( CHOP-TOP COUGHS )
" E-X-I-T . "
" Exit . "
- Good night . - Oh ! Good night !
Good night !
Good night .
( FLESH SIZZLING )
Good night !
( IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE ) Good night .
( CHUCKLING )
Hey , what about my request ?
You know ,
that Lefty-request record
that you honked out today ?
I love that !
Let 's see .
( MIMICKING BUZZER )
( MIMICKING GUN FIRING )
( SCREAMING )
( CHUCKLING )
What was it , anyway ? The " Rambo III " soundtrack ?
( GRUNTS )
Gonna play it again ?
( COAT HANGER SCREECHING )
Sure would like it .
Hey , maybe I could get a copy ,
and you could autograph it .
To a far-out fan !
( CHUCKLES )
- What 's in here ? - Record vault .
Oh , where you keep the golden oldies ?
And maybe ...
Maybe the new music 's in ...
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
Not me , you dumb-ass !
Get the girl ! Get the girl !
( SCREAMING )
( LEATHERFACE GRUNTING )
( EXCLAIMING )
He dented my plate ! My brain is burning !
Nam flashback ! Nam flashback !
( GROANING )
Leatherface , you bitch , I 'll ...
Look what you did to my Sonny Bono wig-do .
Oh , God damn , I can 't believe it !
You gonna have to buy me a new plate cover !
You gonna have to buy me a new plate cover , Leatherface .
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
( GROANING )
He 's gonna send me back to the VA Hospital
with this dent in my plate .
( GRUNTING )
Well , at least he didn 't mess me up .
Dog will hunt . Get that bitch , Leatherface .
Get that bitch !
( LAUGHS )
Dog will hunt .
( LEATHERFACE YELLING )
( SCREAMING )
Go away !
Shit . Humble Pie !
( LAUGHING )
Hurry up , Leatherface . Hurry up . Get that bitch !
Go away !
( EXCLAIMING )
( CHUCKLES )
Music is my life !
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
( GROANING )
They live on fear . They live on fear . They live on fear .
( MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO )
( MIMICKING DRUMS BEATING )
( SINGING )
Stretch , darling , you know the door 's unlocked ?
( CLATTERING )
Hey !
What the shit ?
Hey ! Lick my plate , you dog dick !
What the fuck you think you 're doing in here ,
you crazy-looking little son of a bitch ?
Get out of here !
( L.G. SCREAMING )
( L.G. SHOUTING )
( CHUCKLES )
Time for incoming mail !
( LAUGHING )
Ho Chi Minh !
( L.G. YELLING )
A-one and a-two and a-three !
( LAUGHING )
Go , you little bitch !
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
( SCREAMING )
( CHAINSAW SCRAPING )
( SOBBING )
( RATTLING )
( SCREAMING )
Go away ! Leave me alone !
( GASPING )
( STRETCH GASPING )
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
( MIMICKING SCREAMING )
( LAUGHING )
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
No , no , no , no ! God , no , please don 't !
Incoming mail !
No , no , no !
No , no , no , please , God , no !
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
No , no , no , please , God ! Please , God , no !
No !
No , no , no , please , God ! Stop it ! God , no !
No , no , please , God !
( PANTING )
Are you mad at me ?
How mad at me are you ?
( SOBBING )
You 're not really mad at me .
( GASPING )
How good are you ?
Huh ?
( LEATHERFACE GASPING )
CHOP-TOP : Get that bitch , Leatherface ! Get that bitch !
( WHISPERING ) How good
are you ?
Oh .
Really ?
Are you really , really
good ?
Are you really good ?
You 're really good .
( GRUNTING )
( WHISPERS ) You 're the best .
Oh , no .
( SCREAMING )
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
No ! No !
Please don 't kill me !
No , God !
No , please , God !
( GRUNTING )
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
No , God !
Oh , God ! Oh , God !
Leatherface .
( CHOP-TOP LAUGHS )
Did you get her , Bubba ? Did you get that bitch ?
She was my fave , but she knew .
And now , nobody knows .
Look what you did to my plate , you bitch !
You got her ? Did you get her good ?
Slap me five .
( CHUCKLING )
I got one , too .
A bonus body !
( LAUGHING )
Look at that beef .
Help me get it out of here .
CHOP-TOP : Whoa .
Ooh !
( CHUCKLING )
Giddyup !
( BICYCLE HORN HONKING )
No , they 'll get away .
No , no , they 'll get away .
They can 't get away .
( ENGINE STARTING )
God damn it , Lefty . You 're late .
Damn it , Lefty .
( GASPING )
No !
( SOBBING )
ENRIGHT : Stretch !
Lefty ?
( SCREAMS )
Stretch !
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
Hold on !
Grab onto something . Hold onto it .
Lefty , they came ! Where were you ?
I had to do it . Damn , I used you , girl .
I 'm here now . Grab hold of this .
Grab hold of this , now . Don 't you cry , little sister . I 'm here now .
Come on , I 'm here now . You can get it . Come on , now .
You got it . Come on .
( GROANS )
Come on ! Grab it !
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
( SOBBING )
( SCREAMING )
( GASPING )
( SCREAMS )
Oh , my God .
Oh , Lord , help me beat this stranger that walks beside me ,
that takes away my strength .
Lord , you show me the end .
Show me what I fear so I don 't fear it no more .
( SCREAMING )
It 's the devil 's playground .
( WHIRRING )
I 'm bringing it down ! Down to hell !
Bring it all down !
( SCREAMING )
( PEOPLE CHATTERING )
COOK : I hate to say it ,
but that hillbilly hog you boys got earlier is the tops tonight .
CHOP-TOP : That 's mine ! Mine ! Not Bubba 's . Me ! Me !
Bust it up !
Wanna go to the movies ?
No crowds . Everybody 's at the football parties .
COOK : Tonight 's a washout .
Biggest meat-eater weekend of the month , and we 're gonna lose money on it .
Damn it all ! Maybe we just ought to quit .
CHOP-TOP : Oh , yeah ? Kiss my plate , Mr. Big Shot . Maybe you forgot .
This chromedome bankrolled this food business .
No lucky goof with a machete , no head wound .
No head wound , no fancy rolling grill a-go-go .
Ain 't no fool . Kiss it . Don 't forget it .
( WHIRRING )
Peel that pig and slice him thick .
- That 's my sweet pea . - Get them hogs on the grill .
Big , big pre-game brunch tomorrow means a ton of croissant sandwiches .
Oh , I love this town .
Hey , you nitwit , get back in here and get that grill going .
( ELECTRIC KNIFE WHIRRING )
( GRUNTING )
( BUZZING )
( MOANING )
( FLY BUZZING )
( BUZZING )
( FLESH TEARING )
( CRYING )
( GRUNTING ANGRILY )
( SCREAMS )
( SOBBING )
( GRUNTING )
No . No . No good .
No good .
( GROANING )
Come on , Bubba . Cook 's out here , and he 's chewing ass like it was steak .
" You gotta run for that money now . "
" Chase that dollar . Gotta go fast to catch it . "
You dumb baboozer . Too dumb to even close the door .
I 'm tired of kicking your asses .
What are you doing ? You trying to hide something ?
( LEATHERFACE GRUNTING )
Get that eyeball pậté working .
Hey , you coon shit , where are you going ?
COOK : We need the club sandwiches ...
( WHISPERING ) Help . Help me . Please .
Please , help me .
Can you help me get out of here ?
What is it ? Put that down . Put that down .
Put that down .
What is that ?
Is it wet ? It 's wet . Put it down .
( SOBBING )
( CRYING )
( LEATHERFACE GRUNTS )
( STRETCH GRUNTING )
( CRYING )
( GROANS )
( STRETCH SOBBING )
( GROANING )
( GASPING )
( GRUNTING )
( SOBBING )
( EXCLAIMING )
( L.G. GRUNTING )
( SCREAMING )
( GRUNTS )
( SOBBING )
( HAWKS )
My darling .
( SOBS )
Darling ?
Don 't be scared , darling .
( SCREAMING )
STRETCH : Oh , no , L.G.
Oh , no . Oh , no .
L.G. !
STRETCH : Oh , my God !
L.G. , they got you , too ?
Oh , L.G. !
( L.G. HAWKING )
( L.G. SPITTING )
We gotta get y 'all loose .
( L.G. GRUNTING )
I guess I 'm falling apart on you , honey .
( STRETCH SOBBING )
L.G. : No .
No .
( SIGHS )
Shit .
( SOBBING )
L.G. ,
I love you .
( RUMBLING )
( CHOP-TOP LAUGHING )
COOK : So he says ,
" Hey , get me those lawyers . Legal meat . "
CHOP-TOP : Legal meat , yeah !
COOK : Bubba , you idiot ! Get your ass over here .
- You fucked up again . - CHOP-TOP : You fucked up again .
COOK : He says , " Hey , get me those lawyers . "
" Legal meat , y 'all . "
Fuck me in the left eye !
( COOK LAUGHING )
COOK : Valuable kill-time wasted running down them cooped-up pencil necks ,
and not a good chop on the whole bunch .
I pick the vittles . Get it ?
- I. Me . Nobody but ... - CHOP-TOP : I pick the vittles , I.
COOK : Bubba , you hull wreckage ! CHOP-TOP : Me . Nobody but ...
COOK : Busted again , huh ? That 's the main support beam .
( CREAKING )
Fuck , you idiots ! You both will pay !
( LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY )
Both of you ... You 're both ...
Look what your brother 's done now . You coon shit .
COOK : You cut the main support beam . And this is what happens .
Of course this is what happens .
That big brute !
Dirty meat don 't cut it .
Family standards only require the best meat in town .
More money lost .
I never , never , never get a break .
Work , work night and day ,
presenting myself to the people , selling , selling .
You pair of prima donnas fooling around here and listening to the radio all day
and sawing down your own house .
( BUZZING )
Take it all down !
Bring it all down !
Bury the devil !
May the Lord have mercy on our souls !
( SCREAMING )
Get that thing out of here .
Maybe it cracked the main butane tank .
It 's up there . Go look at it .
Taxes . Taxes .
Damn property taxes fuck up everything .
COOK : Crooks don 't pay taxes . Politicians don 't .
Movie stars don 't .
It 's the little guy that can 't make a dime . He pays the taxes .
Small businessman gets it in the ass every time .
COOK : I ought to quit .
CHOP-TOP : Right , it 's junk . Quit . Dump this cook show .
Sell off this turkey . It 's time . It 's in the air .
It 's what the public wants .
I don 't wanna hear that again .
It 's Nam Land !
( STRETCH SCREAMS )
( CHOP-TOP EXCLAIMING )
CHOP-TOP : What the hell was that ?
( IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE ) I don 't know , boy .
It looked like a big , big fireball .
( LAUGHING )
Nam Land .
CHOP-TOP : Napalm .
Fire in the hole .
( WHOOPS )
COOK : That 's the main butane tank up there , Bubba .
Go look at it . Get your butt moving , boy .
Go up there and look at it . Go look at it .
- I 'll kick you in the ass again . - Not now . It 's Nam Land .
- It 's a hit . It 's a bang . It 's a smash . - Shut him up , Bubba .
Did you see it ?
Well , did you ? Didn 't you ?
Did you ? Didn 't you ?
Go check it out , boy .
- Nam Land ! - Oh , shut up !
( SNICKERING )
I told you to go check it out , boy , before I start kicking your ass .
Some kind of crazy booger just skipped through here .
No , a booger ? How big ?
A big crazy booger . Let 's haul butt , bro .
( BUZZING )
Oh , my God .
Oh , God .
Franklin .
Don 't you cry , my brother .
I 'm here now .
They can 't do this .
They can 't do this !
( CHAINSAW BUZZING )
They can 't do this ! They can 't do this !
I 'll take you back to hell !
I 'll take you to hell !
( SOBBING )
( CRYING )
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
( SCREAMING )
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
All right , all right !
Let 's talk about it .
Okay . What , are you pissed-off ? What about me ?
Listen , this is not gonna work out .
( SOBBING )
I 'm trying to be open with you . It 's nobody 's fault . I just can 't do this .
Let me go .
COOK : What the hell 's going on here ?
Uh-oh .
Bubba , you nap-haired idiot .
Get out of here .
Who 's this ? I get it .
Are you the saboteur that 's fucking up our house ?
( COOK LAUGHING )
COOK : Trying to put me out of business ?
Thousands of dollars lost .
You got that kind of money ? No !
It 's the deejay . My fave .
That dirty thing ?
COOK : Told me you boys got her .
CHOP-TOP : Well , yeah .
Leatherface killed her once already tonight .
But look , she 's red-faced .
Bubba 's been playing with her . Bubba likes her .
Bubba 's got a girlfriend .
( SINGSONGING ) Bubba 's got a girlfriend ! Bubba 's got a girlfriend !
Bubba 's got a girlfriend ! Bubba 's got a girlfriend !
Bubba 's got a girl ...
( LAUGHING )
COOK : Is that what this is , Bubba ?
The old cock-and-cunt swindle , huh ?
S-C-E-X . Sex .
And you had to find out about it , didn 't you ?
COOK : You just couldn 't leave it alone .
If you wanted to know about it so bad , why didn 't you ask me ?
You wanna know about it ? You wanna know about it ?
Ask me . Ask me .
It 's a swindle , that 's all . So don 't get mixed up in it .
Help me . Help me .
Help me .
Please , help me . Please .
Please , help me .
All right , Miss Priss , cut that out .
Leave him alone , damn it !
Bubba , you were supposed to finish her . Finish her now .
- Burn her like a rat . - Finish her .
- Burn her like a rat ! - Finish her now .
Burn her like a rat ! Burn her like a rat , rat , rat !
- Burn her like a rat ! - Finish her now !
- Finish her now , Bubba ! - Burn her like a rat !
COOK : Finish her ! CHOP-TOP : Finish her . Finish her .
Give me that .
Turn traitor for a piece of tail .
You got one choice , boy , sex or the saw .
Sex is , well , nobody knows .
But the saw , the saw is family .
- The saw is family . - Wait till Granddad hears about this .
Take her away .
- She 's in the garbage now . - Oh , no .
- Oh , no . - A-one
and a-two
and three !
No !
( SCREAMING )
Dinnertime , damn it ! Let 's go .
Eat and run . Eat and run .
There 's a lot of hungry football fans to feed .
Hurry it up . Grandpa likes to go fast .
He always did . Come on . Come on .
Time eats money .
( LAUGHING )
Those damn coon shits are the weight of the family .
I stoop my shoulders taking care of my younger brothers .
It squashed the young years out of my life
like a can of cheese whip .
( BELL RINGING )
I wouldn 't wish this rotten life off on a one-eyed ferret with mange .
You 're the first girl Bubba 's brought home to dinner .
This is a real special occasion .
Grandpa sure looks forward to meeting you .
He 's 137 years old but still as fast as Jesse James ,
so don 't you worry none .
Here comes Grandpa now .
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
God bless you , Grandpa .
( SINGSONGING ) Oh , it 's playtime ! It 's dinnertime !
Your little boys have some left here for you .
Yes , no , yes , no ! Yes , we do !
We love you ! We love you !
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
CHOP-TOP : Okay , now . Take it easy , now . Take it easy with Grandpa .
- That 's right . That 's right . - COOK : Get him over here easy , now .
CHOP-TOP : That 's right . Okay . GRANDPA : Come on , you boys .
CHOP-TOP : Easy with Grandpa , now .
- CHOP-TOP : Oh , easy with Grandpa . - No ! No !
STRETCH : Oh , please , no .
Don 't rattle him like that , damn it !
You 're balling up his shit .
No !
Grandpa 's strict liquid diet keeps him as fresh as a rose .
Every spring ,
the Atlas Rendering Company used to throw a big barbecue for Grandpa .
Oh , he was the master .
He was the one and only .
He showed us all the business .
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
We was raised in meat .
( LAUGHING )
But then after the glory , here comes the shame .
Atlas went for automation .
The electrified cages ,
the cold-steel chutes ,
the air-powered head hammers .
That drove Grandpa crazy , seeing things done like that .
Let me go ! Let me go !
No , no , that 's all right . That 's all right . It 'll be over soon .
( MOANING )
Get the hammer .
The crunching and the grinding ,
he just couldn 't stand it , no way .
COOK : So that was all she wrote .
One morning , Grandpa just quit going in .
It was the shame .
( WHIMPERING )
It was the shame . The shame .
There 's more work to do . Let 's get on with it .
Right . Let 's get on with it . Bingo !
Give me that . Get that tub over there in a hurry .
Do I have to do every damn thing around here ?
You just sit tight .
( SCREAMS )
Bubba , she 's ready . Bring her on down .
No !
( SQUEAKING )
- Oh , no ! - Bring her on down , damn it !
STRETCH : No ! No !
Bring her on down !
No ! No , no , no !
No , no , no !
( SOBBING )
STRETCH : Help me ! No , no , no !
Let me go ! You gotta let me go ! Let me go ! Please , help me !
- This will be one you won 't forget . - Please , help me !
It 's a real honor .
Grandpa , he 's a one-hitter .
And it 's just like going home .
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
Please help me !
- No ! No ! No , God ! - No , no .
Help me ! Let me go !
Let me go ! Let me go !
( LAUGHING )
Help me , please !
Please , help me !
Let 's go see Grandpa , boy .
No , don 't !
- No ! No , God ! - Come on . Bring the bitch down .
No ! No ! No !
No , no , let me go !
Let me go !
Let me go ! No ! No !
No , no , no !
( CHOP-TOP LAUGHING )
No !
Here come the judge . Here come the judge .
Now , don 't ruin Grandpa 's favorite rug .
Be careful of the splatter . You gotta be careful of the splatter .
Oh , Great-grandma in chainsaw heaven ...
No ! No ! God !
... please don 't hoodoo the boy .
Hey , Grandpa , here 's the big boy .
Look what Bubba brought you .
Hey , Grandpa , Bubba 's got something to show you here .
Look , a Slurpee booty .
( LAUGHING )
- CHOP-TOP : Hit her , Grandpa . - Come on , Grandpa .
Let 's see you do it . Now , come on . Come on , Grandpa . You 're the best .
- Hit her , Grandpa . Hit her ! - Come on . Hit her , Grandpa .
Come on , I 'm telling you ...
Remember those thieves ? Come on . One-hitter .
- Come on , Grandpa . - Hit her . Hit her , Grandpa .
Come on , you won 't miss her .
( SCREAMING )
- Come on , Grandpa . - Come on , Grandpa .
Hit her . Hit that bitch . Hit that bitch .
Come on , Grandpa .
Come on , Grandpa . You can do it . You 're the best .
Come on , there , Grandpa . Come on , there , Grandpa .
( STRETCH SCREAMING )
Hit her , Grandpa . Come on , Grandpa .
You 're the best , Grandpa .
Hit that bitch , Grandpa . Hit her .
Come on , Grandpa . Hit her . You are , Grandpa . You 're the best .
CHOP-TOP : Yeah ! That 's good , isn 't it , Grandpa ?
Grandpa !
COOK : Attaboy , Grandpa . CHOP-TOP : Hit that bitch , now , Grandpa .
- Come on , Grandpa . You can do it . - Get her now , Grandpa . You can do it .
Come on , Grandpa .
( CRASHING )
STRETCH : No ! No ! No !
No ! No ! No ! No !
No ! No !
Hit that bitch . Hit that bitch !
CHOP-TOP : Come on , Grandpa !
( SCREAMS )
Come on , Grandpa !
Oh , Grandpa , let 's get on with it .
All right ! SIurpee-booty time !
( METALLIC CLANGING )
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
( ENRIGHT SINGING )
( CHOP-TOP SINGING ALONG WITH ENRIGHT )
Oh , shut up !
What the hell 's going on here ?
( ENRIGHT SINGING )
( CEILING CREAKING )
( SINGING )
Boys , boys , boys .
What the hell 's going on here ?
Is that the American way of entering a man 's home , singing like that ?
Oh , I get it . The old pressure game , huh ?
Boys , you never should have been doing this .
Who sent you ? Those Sissies over at Del-Mar Catering ?
COOK : That chickenshit burrito-man bunch ?
( COOK CHUCKLING )
Well , I don 't care , you hear ? Yeah , that 's right .
It 's a dog-eat-dog world .
And from where I sit , there just ain 't enough damn dogs .
If you can 't stand the heat , get out of the damn kitchen .
( CHUCKLES )
How much , huh ? Let 's make a deal right here .
Real cash money .
Just you and me , huh ? I don 't care who sent you .
I 'm the Lord of the Harvest .
Who 's that ? Some new health-food bunch ?
Come on . Come on .
Is there any money in it , you wanna know ?
Yeah , right here . How much , huh ? How much ?
( CLATTERING )
- Lefty . - Sister .
Lefty !
Brazos !
( SCREAMING )
Run , sister . Run !
( ENRIGHT GRUNTING )
( LEATHERFACE YELLING )
( YELLING )
( CHUCKLING )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( GRUNTING )
( EXCLAIMING )
Small businessman
that always , always , always gets it in the ass !
Sure ... Sure took care of my hems .
Saved a trip to the hospital .
Looks ... Looks bad .
Sure burned my beads bad on that one .
( LAUGHING )
( GRUNTS )
( SCREAMING )
Maybe it 's time to just shut down .
Time to shut down the show , yeah .
Yeah , pull the plug . Come here , nubbins .
Where ... Where 's that old " Fuck you , Charlie " ?
( SCREAMING )
That little " Just in case , baby " ?
Where 'd you put it ?
Yeah , there it is .
Man ... Man builds a good , sturdy trade
by hooking and crooking .
And then , kerplooey !
The gods just kick him right in the balls .
Oh , no , not this time .
( LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY )
No ! No !
I got the last laugh right here .
( YELLING )
( SCREAMING )
CHOP-TOP : Going down , now !
( STRETCH SCREAMS )
( LAUGHING )
( GROANING )
( EXCLAIMING )
( LAUGHING )
( STRETCH SCREAMS )
Going down ! Going down , now !
( CACKLING )
( CHOP-TOP EXCLAIMS )
( GRUNTING )
Here I come , you hog bitch !
You hog bitch !
Dead end , girl . Dead end now .
Dead-end city .
Look at my face .
Look . Look !
It 's like death eating a cracker , isn 't it ?
Huh ? Huh ?
No !
Get away from her ! Get away !
( EXCLAIMS )
Don 't touch her ! No !
Grandma !
No !
Grandma ! Grandma !
Grandma !
You killed her , you hog bitch !
( STRETCH SCREAMS )
( SCREAMING MANIACALLY )
( CHAINSAW WHIRRING )
Die !
( SCREAMING )